A Guide to the Social Science Research Council records, Administration and Officers Files, Presidents' Office FA1827
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Outside Organizations, 1972-2001; 2; 10.63 Cubic Feet 28 letter document boxes
  - Pew Foundation, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 318)
  - Reynolds Foundation Grant, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 319)
  - Conference on "Research Access" co-sponsored by the Smithsonian Institution and the Social Science Research Council, Washington, D.C., 1985-1986 (Box 24, Folder 320-322)
    Conference November 1985 and includes follow-up reports from 1986
  - Rockefeller Foundation Workshops, 1982-1988 (Box 25, Folder 323)
  - Rockefeller Family Office, 1983-1988 (Box 25, Folder 324)
  - Soviet Rockefeller Program, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 325)
  - Task Force on Persistent Rural Poverty, The Rural Sociological Society, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 326)
  - Alfred P. Sloan - Grant #B1987-49 International Productivity and Competitiveness (Box 25, Folder 327)
  - The Spencer Foundation - Committee on New York City, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 328)
  - The Spencer Foundation - Study of Social Knowledge and Modern Social Policies, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 329)
  - Tinker Foundation - Joint Committee on Latin America Studies (JCLAS) proposal, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 330)
  - SSRC - United Kingdom, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 331)
  - System Development Foundation, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 332)
  - UNICEF, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 333)
  - United Nations University, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 334)
  - Woodrow Wilson National Fellowship Foundation, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 335)
  - Winrock International, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 336)
  - Winston Foundation, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 337)
  - Report: NEH Grant #RI-20592-93 in Support of ACLS-SSRC Post-Doctoral Fellowships in International and Foreign Area Studies, 1993-1994, 1994 March 21 (Box 43, Folder 522)
  - ACLS/SSRC Postdoctoral Fellowships, 1993-1994 (Box 43, Folder 523)
  - Ford Foundation Grant - SSRC #12000 (Research Program on War, the State, and Society Relations in the Middle East after the Gulf War), 1991 (Box 43, Folder 524)
  - Ford Foundation Grant #860-0171-2 - Narrative and Financial Report - Foreign Policy Studies, 1994 March 14 (Box 43, Folder 525)
  - Ford Foundation Grant #820-1035 - Narrative & Financial Report (International Committees), 1991-1992 (Box 43, Folder 527)
  - Ford Foundation - General Correspondence, 1990-1995 (Box 43, Folder 528)
  - Ford Foundation - Narrative & Financial Report - Dissertation Research Fellowships in Foreign Area Studies (Grant #910-1039), 1992-1993 (Box 43, Folder 529)
  - Ford Foundation - Narrative and Financial Report (Foreign Policy Studies), Grant #860-0171-2, 1991-1992 (Box 43, Folder 530)
  - Carnegie Soviet Disunion Project (CEIP), 1994 (Box 43, Folder 531)
  - Carnegie Corporation of New York - Soviet Studies Program Correspondence, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 532)
  - Ford Foundation Grant #900-0504 International Predissertation Fellowship Program (IPFP), 1991-1992 (Box 44, Folder 533)
  - Ford Foundation Grant #900-0504-1 International Predissertation Fellowship Program (IPFP), 1992-1994 (Box 44, Folder 534)
  - Mellon Foundation - Narrative and Financial Report (Dissertation Research Fellowship Grant), 1991-1993 (Box 44, Folder 535)
  - Ford Foundation Grant #850-0885 (Comparative Study of Muslim Societies), 1989-1990 (Box 44, Folder 536)
  - Foreign Area Studies Advisory Group - Letters and Replies, 1990-1994 (Box 44, Folder 537)
  - Foreign Area Studies Advisory Group - Replies (M-R), 1989 (Box 44, Folder 538)
  - Hewlett Foundation, 1992-1995 (Box 44, Folder 539)
  - Kellogg Foundation, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 540)
  - The Henry Luce Foundation, 1991-1993 (Box 44, Folder 541)
  - National Security Education Program (NSEP) - Mailing List(s), 1992 (Box 44, Folder 542)
  - National Security Education Program: A Review and Analysis, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 543)
  - William and Flora Hewlett Foundation, 1990-1992 (Box 45, Folder 544)
  - MacArthur Foundation, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 545)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (Social Science Research Council/American Council of Learned Societies Grant #RI-20472-90), 1991-1993 (Box 45, Folder 546)
  - Core Budgets, 1994 November (Box 45, Folder 547)
    Africa, Japan, Korea, Latin America, Near and Middle East, South Asia, Southeast Asia, Soviet Union and Successor States, Western Europe
  - Ford Foundation - Narrative and Financial Report (Grant #910-1039), 1992-1993 (Box 45, Folder 548)
  - Ford Foundation - Narrative and Financial Report (Grant #910-0695), 1993 (Box 45, Folder 549)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities General Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 45, Folder 550)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities General Correspondence, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 618)
    Restricted – confidential material
  - National Endowment for the Humanities - Post Docs, 1992-1995 (Box 46, Folder 551)
  - SSRC - A Five-Year Program for International Studies, 1990 (Box 46, Folder 552)
  - Ford Foundation - Reports and Correspondence - Comparative Muslim Societies (Grant #850-0885-1), 1991-1994 (Box 46, Folder 553)
  - National Security Education Act (NSEA) of 1991, National Security Education Program (NSEP), 1992-1993 (Box 46, Folder 554)
  - Ford Foundation Grant - Soviet Union/Eastern Europe Economies Workshop (Grant #840-0870-5), 1993 (Box 46, Folder 555)
  - Ford Foundation Grant #820-1035 (International Programs Five-Year Core Grant), 1989-1991 (Box 46, Folder 556)
  - Foundation for Educational Exchange Between Canada and the USA, The Fulbright Program, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 557)
  - National Security Education Program (NSEP), 1994 (Box 46, Folder 558)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities - General Correspondence, 1993-1995 (Box 47, Folder 559)
  - Foreign Area Studies Advisory Group - Letters and Replies (S-Y), 1989 (Box 47, Folder 560)
  - The Tinker Foundation - Recommendation Letter, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 561)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - Central European Universities Project, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 562)
  - Russian Science Foundation (RSF), 1993 (Box 47, Folder 563)
  - Suntory Foundation, 1990 (Box 47, Folder 564)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - Letter to William S. Moody, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 565)
  - SSRC-National Endowment for the Humanities - Post-doctorate Competition Allocations, 1993-1994 (Box 47, Folder 566)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (SSRC/ACLS Grant #RI-20264-86), 1991 (Box 47, Folder 567)
  - National Security Education Act of 1991 (NSEA), 1992 (Box 47, Folder 568)
  - ACLS/SSRC National Endowment for the Humanities - Fellowships in International and Foreign Area Studies, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 569)
  - Ford Foundation - Narrative and Financial Report - Dissertation Research Fellowships in Foreign Area Studies (Grant #910-1039), 1994 (Box 48, Folder 570)
  - Final Performance Report - National Endowment for the Humanities Grant RI #20472-90, 1993 March 31 (Box 48, Folder 571)
  - Stanley J. Heginbotham Correspondence - National Endowment for the Humanities - Fellowships in International and Area Studies, 1994-1995 (Box 48, Folder 572)
- David Featherman Files, 1979-1995; 3; 3.42 Cubic Feet 9 letter document boxes
  David Featherman served as president of the SSRC from 1989-1995. His files consist of correspondence with foundations and nonprofit organizations, research materials, trip files, grant and project proposals, meeting materials, articles, and SSRC workshop files. Some files may contain correspondence and other documents of Stanley Heginbotham, Vice President of the SSRC during David Featherman's tenure.
  - Gerald Nadler/David Featherman Project - Sustainable Industrial and Human Productivity, 1990-1993 (Box 25, Folder 338-340)
  - Beijing Trip, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 341)
  - Korea/China Trip File, 1991-1993 (Box 25, Folder 342)
  - North Korea Initiative, 1991-1994 (Box 25, Folder 343)
  - Vietnam, Laos, and Cambodia, 1991-1992 (Box 26, Folder 344)
  - Tarrow, Sidney Proposal (A Study of the Effects of Recent Changes in Europe on European Studies in the U.S.), 1991-1993 (Box 26, Folder 345-346)
  - Trip Files - Korea Foundation, Korea Research Foundation, and Korea Development Institute, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 347)
  - National Science Foundation - Urban Infrastructure, 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 348)
  - Indochina Initiative, 1991-1993 (Box 26, Folder 349)
  - Vietnam Initiative, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 350)
  - United States-Mexico Foundation for Science, 1991-1992 (Box 26, Folder 351)
  - Proposal for an SSRC Committee on Transnational Interactions in Contemporary Societies, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 352)
  - Taiwan, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 353)
  - Margaret Levi - Proposed Initiative on Political Economy, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 354)
  - Minority Affairs Program (MAP) - Minority Fellowship Program, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 355)
  - Policy Conference on Persistent Urban Poverty, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 356)
  - Joint Committee on the Soviet Union and its Successor States (JCSSS)/Pan-Europe Working Group (PEWG), 1993 (Box 27, Folder 357)
  - International SSRC Programs - Background, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 358)
  - Indochina Scholarly Exchange Program (ISEP), 1991-1992 (Box 27, Folder 359)
  - B.L. Turner II, Proposal (Global Land Use/Cover Change Project), 1993 (Box 27, Folder 360)
  - Lawrence Sullivan, Project Outline - Religious Regimes in Contact: Christian Mission, Global Religious Transformations, and the Study of Religion, 1991-1993 (Box 27, Folder 361)
  - SSRC, International Social Science Council (ISSC), and Development Alternatives with Women for New Era Proposal (Recasting the Population-Environment Debate), 1991 (Box 27, Folder 362)
  - SSRC/International Research and Exchanges Board (IREX) Proposal (Data Resources and Data Needs for Resources and Policy in the European Economies in Transition), 1993 May (Box 27, Folder 363)
  - Silverberg, Helene Proposal (Gender and the Origins of American Social Science), 1992 August (Box 27, Folder 364)
  - Muslim Studies Proposal to Ford Foundation, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 365)
  - Mingming, Shen Proposal (A Proposal for Expansion and Development of the Research Center for Contemporary China at Peking University), 1994 (Box 27, Folder 366)
  - Lytle, Paula Franklin Proposal Draft (Agarian Studies Program), 1990 (Box 27, Folder 367)
  - Joint Committee on the Soviet Union and its Successor States (JCSSS) Proposal to Eurasia Foundation, 1992 April 28 (Box 27, Folder 368)
  - HUD Proposal (Application for Research Assistance Grant), 1993-1995 (Box 27, Folder 369)
  - House, Robert J. Proposal (The Globe Leadership and Organizational Behavior Effectiveness Research Program (GLOBE)), 1995 (Box 27, Folder 370)
  - Holzner, Buckart, Discussion Paper (Institutional Strategies for Internationalization of Higher Education), 1995 (Box 27, Folder 371)
  - Hayes, Margaret Daly Proposal (The Impact of Structural Reforms, Market Opening and Integration on Entrepreneurs and Enterprises in Latin America: The View from the Private Sector), 1992 (Box 28, Folder 372)
  - Greenough, Paul Proposal ("Social Science and Immunization Project Proposal for Comparative Research Studies in Asia, Europe, and America), 1991-1994 (Box 28, Folder 373-374)
  - Global Environmental Change Proposal (Prospectus: State of the Art for Research on Land-Use Change), 1990 (Box 28, Folder 375)
  - Russian Social Science Initiative, 1991-1992 (Box 28, Folder 376)
  - International Program Meetings, 1993-1994 (Box 28, Folder 377)
  - SSRC and ACLS Chairs Meetings, 1993-1994 (Box 28, Folder 378)
  - Psychology at SSRC - Articles and Correspondence, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 379)
  - Sumi Jones - Nichibunken Grant, Joint Committee for Japanese Studies (JCJS), 1991-1992 (Box 28, Folder 380)
  - International Program Regrant, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 381)
  - Richards, John F. Proposal (Comparative Examination of Landed Property Rights), 1992-1993 (Box 29, Folder 382)
  - Levi, Margaret, Robert Bates, et al, A Proposal for Joint Research, 1990-1991 (Box 29, Folder 383)
  - Latin America Committee Proposal (Program on the Political Economy of Development), 1991 (Box 29, Folder 384)
  - Keohane, Robert O. and Helen Milner Project (International Relations and Domestic Politics), 1993-1994 (Box 29, Folder 385)
  - Keohane, Robert O. & Judith Goldstein Proposal (Ideas and Foreign Policy), 1990-1993 (Box 29, Folder 386)
  - Katz, Michael and Michelle Fine Proposal (Urban School Reform), 1994 (Box 29, Folder 387)
  - German-American Academic Council Proposal (Summer Academies for Young International Scholars), 1992-1993 (Box 29, Folder 388)
  - Gemelli, Giuliana Project Proposal (Intellectual Cooperation in Europe During the 20th Century), 1990 (Box 29, Folder 389)
  - Dror, Judith Proposal (Buddhism and the Construction, Institutionalization, and Transmission of the Centralized State in China, Korea, and Japan), 1993 (Box 29, Folder 390)
  - Coen, Robert and Bert Hickman Proposal ("Econometric Modelling of Economies in Transition") - Mellon Foundation, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 391)
  - Brightman, Robert A. - Symposium Proposal (Theory in Anthropology), 1991 (Box 29, Folder 392)
  - Basu, Amrita Proposal (Hindu Nationalism and the Crisis of State Legitimacy in India), 1993 (Box 29, Folder 393)
  - Andrews, Reid and Herrick Chapman Proposal (Social Construction of Democracy), 1990-1991 (Box 29, Folder 394)
  - Japan Trip, 1992 November (Box 29, Folder 395)
  - Project on African Agriculture, 1991-1992 (Box 30, Folder 396)
  - Agriculture Project - Other Funding Sources, 1993-1994 (Box 30, Folder 397)
  - SSRC Africa Program Fellowships for Training and Dissertation Research (FTDR) Workshop Proposals, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 398)
  - Workshop on Population and Environment, Mexico - Planning, 1989-1991 (Box 30, Folder 399-400)
  - Fellowships for Training and Dissertation Research (FTDR) Workshop Participants, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 401)
  - Fellowships for Training and Dissertation Research (FTDR) Workshop, 1988 October (Box 30, Folder 402)
  - African Agriculture Fellowships for Training and Dissertation Research (FTDR) Workshop Planning, 1991-1992 (Box 31, Folder 403)
  - Fellowships for Training and Dissertation Research (FTDR) Workshop, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 404)
  - Fellowships for Training and Dissertation Research (FTDR) Workshop - Travel and Accommodations, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 405)
  - Workshop on Population and Environment Working Paper - Reviewers, 1990-1992 (Box 31, Folder 406)
  - Working Paper Series of the Project on African Agriculture - Mailing List, 1988-1991 (Box 31, Folder 407)
  - Working Paper Series of the Project on African Agriculture - Responses, 1990-1991 (Box 31, Folder 408)
  - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation Correspondence, 1982-1993 (Box 31, Folder 409)
  - Robert Schalkenbach Foundation - Social Science Quotations, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 410)
  - Committee for Research on Global Environmental Change - Rockefeller Foundation Grant GIA GE 0941, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 411)
  - Grants - National Science Foundation, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 412)
  - Hungarian Academy of Science and National Science Foundation Workshop, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 413)
  - SSRC Committee on Global Environmental Change - National Science Foundation Grants, 1991-1993 (Box 31, Folder 414)
  - National Science Foundation - General, 1980-1990 (Box 31, Folder 415-416)
  - Smith-Richardson Foundation, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 417)
  - Spencer Foundation, 1980-1991 (Box 32, Folder 418)
  - Spencer Foundation - Fellowships in Education, 1985-1986 (Box 32, Folder 419)
  - Spencer Foundation - Social Knowledge, 1987-1989 (Box 32, Folder 420)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 421)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1981-1994 (Box 32, Folder 422-423)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - African Agriculture, 1984-1989 (Box 32, Folder 424)
  - Russell Sage Foundation - Social Science Quotations Project, 1988-1991 (Box 32, Folder 425)
  - Russell Sage Foundation - Hispanic Communities, 1988-1992 (Box 32, Folder 426)
  - Russell Sage Foundation - SSRC Committee on New York City, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 427)
  - Russell Sage Foundation - Urban Poverty, 1988-1993 (Box 32, Folder 428)
  - Russell Sage Foundation Correspondence, 1981-1994 (Box 32, Folder 429)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - Culture and Health Proposal, 1992-1993 (Box 32, Folder 430)
  - Ford Foundation - Bangladesh Program, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 431)
  - Inner Asia Committee - Possibilities Meeting, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 432)
  - South Asia Committee - Wenner-Gren Foundation, 1988-1989 (Box 32, Folder 433)
  - Volkswagen Foundation, 1980-1989 (Box 32, Folder 434)
  - Suntory Foundation Correspondence, 1986-1990 (Box 32, Folder 435)
  - The Toyota Foundation, 1990-1994 (Box 32, Folder 436)
  - Sasakawa Peace Foundation, 1989-1992 (Box 32, Folder 437)
  - International Social Science Council (ISSC) Membership Information, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 438)
  - The Christopher Reynolds Foundation - Indochina Scholarly Exchange Program (ISEP), 1991 (Box 33, Folder 439)
  - Possible AIDS Project, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 440)
  - International Social Science Council (ISSC) Liaison Committee, 1993-1995 (Box 33, Folder 441)
  - The Pew Charitable Trusts, 1989-1994 (Box 33, Folder 442)
  - National Science Foundation (NSF) Reorganization Meeting, 1979-1990 (Box 33, Folder 443)
  - National Science Board - Committee on the Twelfth Board Report, "Survey Research and Opinion Polls", 1980-1981 (Box 33, Folder 444)
- Executive Committee Meetings, 1980-1995; 4; 1.9 Cubic Feet 5 letter document boxes
  Contains executive meeting minutes, agendas, correspondence related to issues to be discussed at meetings, committee membership lists, and nomination materials.
  - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, Agendas, and Correspondence, 1985-1988 (Box 33, Folder 445-454)
  - Executive Committee Business, 1986-1988 (Box 33, Folder 455)
  - Executive Committee - Project LINK Correspondence, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 456)
  - Executive Committee - China Area Studies, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 457)
  - Executive Committee - Meeting, 1987 June (Box 33, Folder 458-460)
    Meeting minutes
    Request Funds from National Endowment for the Humanities, 1987
  - Executive Committee - December Meeting, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 461-463)
    Grant approval correspondence
    Meeting minutes from June 1986 meeting
    Meeting schedule and agenda
  - Executive Committee - June Meeting, 1986 (Box 34, Folder 464-466)
    General material
    Condo for Council President
    Meeting organization
  - Executive Committee - December Meeting, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 467-470)
    General meeting materials
    Kenneth Prewitt departure
    Kenneth Prewitt Farewell
  - Executive Committee - June Meeting, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 471-472)
  - Executive Committee - December Meeting, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 473-476)
    Financial Statement
    Agenda
  - Executive Committee - June Meeting, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 477)
  - Executive Committee - December Meeting, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 478)
  - Executive Committee - May Meeting, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 479)
  - Executive Committee - December Meeting, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 480)
  - Executive Committee - May Meeting, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 481)
  - Investment Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 35, Folder 482)
  - Executive Committee - January Meeting, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 483)
  - Executive Committee - October Meeting, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 484-485)
  - Executive Committee - June Meeting, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 486-487)
  - Executive Committee - January Meeting, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 488-490)
  - Executive Committee - October Meeting, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 491-492)
  - General Administration Expenses Memo, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 493)
  - Executive Committee - May Meeting, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 494)
  - Investment Committee, 1988-1991 (Box 36, Folder 495-498)
  - Liberalization and Foreign Policy, Miles Kahler, ed. - Correspondence, Revisions, and Conference Materials, 1992-1995 (Box 36, Folder 499)
  - Executive Mail Ballot - Foreign Policy Studies, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 522)
    Restricted - Executive Search - Open in 2027
  - Mail Ballot - Chair of Near and Middle East, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 523)
  - Issues for Executive Meeting, 1987 December (Box 42, Folder 524)
    Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2037
  - Western Europe Mail Ballot, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 525)
  - New Executive Committee Members, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 526)
  - ACLS Members - China Grants and Committee on Eastern Europe, 1988 (Box 42, Folder 527)
    Restricted - Executive Search - Open in 2028
  - Executive Committee Agenda Item, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 528)
    Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2059
  - Martha Gephart - Personal, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 529)
  - Mail Ballot - Hispanic Committee Members, 1988 (Box 42, Folder 530)
  - Support Staff Salaries, 1988 (Box 42, Folder 531)
    Restricted - Personnel - Open in 2058
- Presidents' Chronological Files, 1986-1993; 5; 2.66 Cubic Feet 7 letter document boxes
  Arrangement
  Folders are arranged reverse chronologically with newer correspondence being closer to the front of each folder.
  Contains SSRC presidents' correspondence from 1986-1993.
  - Frederic Wakeman, Jr. Chronological Files, 1986 September-1989 May (Box 36, Folder 500, Box 37, Folder 501-503, Box 38, Folder 504-505)
  - Frederic Wakeman, Jr. and David L. Featherman Chronological Files, 1989 June-October (Box 38, Folder 506)
  - David L. Featherman Chronological Files, 1989 November-1993 (Box 39, Folder 507-510, Box 40, Folder 511-514, Box 41, Folder 515-518, Box 42, Folder 519-521)
- Committee Overview Files, 1990-1995; 6; 2.66 Cubic Feet 7 letter document boxes
  Primarily contains correspondence related to the work of SSRC committees.
  - Europe Program - Europe Advisory Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 573)
  - The Berlin Program, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 574)
  - Economic Stability and Growth, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 575)
  - Korean Studies, 1990-1993 (Box 48, Folder 576)
  - Japanese Studies - Rockefeller Brothers Fund (RBF) - Intellectual Exchange with Japan, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 577)
  - Committee on New York City, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 578)
  - Europe Program - Pan-Europe Working Group (PEWG), 1992-1994 (Box 49, Folder 579)
  - Near and Middle East, 1990-1992 (Box 49, Folder 580)
  - Urban Underclass, 1990-1994 (Box 49, Folder 581)
  - Latin America, 1990-1992 (Box 49, Folder 582)
  - South/Southeast Asia, 1990-1994 (Box 49, Folder 583)
  - Global Environmental Change, 1990-1993 (Box 50, Folder 584)
  - Japan/East Asia, 1992-1994 (Box 50, Folder 585)
  - Abe Fellowships, 1992-1994 (Box 50, Folder 586)
  - International Peace and Security - Mid-Course Review, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 587)
  - International Peace and Security Memo (Richard Rockwell) on Evaluation and Documentary Materials, 1990-1993 (Box 50, Folder 588)
  - Soviet Central Asia, 1990-1991 (Box 50, Folder 589)
  - Latin American Studies - Journals Projects, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 591)
  - Foreign Policy Studies, 1990-1994 (Box 51, Folder 592)
  - East European Task Force, 1991-1992 (Box 51, Folder 593)
  - Soviet Studies - Title VIII Workshop, 1992 (Box 51, Folder 594)
  - Soviet Studies, 1990-1993 (Box 51, Folder 595-596)
  - Southeast Asia - Indochina, 1990-1991 (Box 51, Folder 597)
  - Chinese Studies, 1990-1994 (Box 51, Folder 598)
  - African Studies, 1990-1994 (Box 52, Folder 599)
  - Abe Fellowship, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 600)
  - International Programs, 1992-1993 (Box 52, Folder 601)
  - Culture, Health, and Human Development, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 602)
  - Contemporary Hispanic Issues, 1991-1992 (Box 52, Folder 603)
  - China Committee Fall 1990 Meeting (Box 52, Folder 604)
  - China Committee - Joint Advisory Committee on International Programs, 1990-1993 (Box 52, Folder 605)
  - Foreign Policy Studies - Foreign Policy Conference Papers, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 606)
  - Latin America Program, 1992-1995 (Box 53, Folder 607)
  - Soviet Studies, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 608)